

# **Profile**

10+ year's customer service experience specializing in team environments with high expectations for excellent communication, response to customer requests, and process redesign.

As a career change I have recently graduated from two separate coding bootcamp programs from Eleven Fifty Academy specializing in Web Development and Software Development.

# **Employment History**

#### Server/Bartender, Turchettis Salumeria, Indianapolis

SEPTEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

Serving and Bartending providing excellent knowledge about the product and service to customers. Currently closed due to COVID-19.

#### Server, Bluebeard, Indianapolis

NOVEMBER 2013 - NOVEMBER 2019

Serving at one of the most highly rated restaurants in the country. Providing excellent knowledge about the products, great service and exceeding in a fast paced team environment.

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

# Education

#### Software Development, Eleven Fifty Academy, Indianapolis

JULY 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

Very passionate about what I learned here and continue to learn. This course helped and pushed me to build applications that I'm very proud of that are listed on my Portfolio.

## Web Development, Eleven Fifty Academy, Indianapolis

APRIL 2020 - JULY 2020

My first course at Eleven Fifty Academy, learning a lot about databases and API's. I'm very proud of the projects I built during this course that are listed on my Portfolio.

OCTOBER 2020 - OCTOBER 2020

# **Details**

317-652-4729 hj.paul7@gmail.com

### Links

<u>LinkedIn</u>

GitHub

# Skills

HTML5

C#

JavaScript

React

API

CSS

TypeScript